icravefreebies.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy « I Crave Freebies

November 8, 2009 · [Leave a Comment](http://www.icravefreebies.com/privacy-policy/#respond)  

This privacy policy applies to the use of ICraveFreebies.com.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

**What information do we collect?**

We provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address.

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

• To communicate with our newsletter subscribers. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**

This website contains links to other sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.icravefreebies.com/terms-of-use>.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on November 08, 2009

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using the information below:
